Eat, Play, Love is a comedy, romance, tv movie
film directed by Christie Will Wolf.
Veterinarian Dr.
Carly Monroe makes it a habit to stop by the local dog shelter as often as possible
because she loves dogs and secretly loves the shelter’s owner, Dan.
Unfortunately, he has agreed to marry his glamorous TV
personality girlfriend and move to the Big Apple.
With Dan’s big move looming, his sister decides to
take matters into her own hands.
Dan Landis, played by Jason Cermak.
Dr. Carly Monroe, played by Jen Lilley.
Michelle Landis, played by Lucie Guest.
Mrs. Gilbert, played by Lindsay Wagner.
Isaac Monroe, played by Lee Majors.
Kristi Waters, played by Emily Maddison.
Eat Pray Love is a 2010 American biographical romantic drama film, directed and
co-written by Ryan Murphy and starring Julia Roberts as Elizabeth Gilbert.
It is based on Gilbert's 2006 memoir, and was released in the United
States on August 13, 2010, to mixed reviews from critics.
The film was a financial success, grossing $205
million against a $60 million budget.
The film explores themes of ex-boyfriend,
veterinarian, dog, makeover, animal shelter.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.